# Aliya Jackson

Philadelphia, PA 1234\$ aliyajaekson@exarripLe.com (123)456-7890 LinkedIn I Portfolio

A Content Writer with eight years of experience specializing in public relations, content development, journalism, and blog writing. A strong history of delivering impactful articles and blog posts to expand awareness of non-profit initiatives and social inequities.

## **Education**

# Bachelor of Arts (B.A.) Journalism

Temple University, Philadelphia, PA September 2012 - June 2016

## **Key Skills**

- Content Writing
- Blog Writing
- Brand Messaging
- Public Relations
- Journalism

### **Certifications**

- Creative Writing Certification, Coursera, 2017
- Content Strategy for Professionals Specialization, Northwestern University, 2016

## **Professional Experience**

#### Content Writer

Better Health Advocates, Philadelphia, PA | October 2018 - Present

- Developed compelling content, blog posts, web copy, and articles for a non-profit advocacy group focused on inequities within the healthcare space, which resulted in a 300% increase in web traffic and a 250% increase in newsletter subscribers
- Conducted research on a wide range of healthcare topics and created informative articles covering the disparity in healthcare access and delivery in diverse communities
- Published three major case studies on healthcare inequity, which included interviewing over 200+ patients and medical professionals

#### Content Writer

Ascend Non-Profit, Philadelphia, PA I June 2016 - October 2018

- Developed content for social media marketing, articles, blog posts, and web pages for a non-profit organization centered around career services for female professionals
- Collaborated with subject matter experts to craft high-quality content to raise awareness of various initiatives to drive the professional development of women